http://leg.mt.gov/privacy

Laws/Statutes
Montana State Statutes (MCA)
By Address
By Name (Legislator Roster)
General Information
Please Note: Internet streaming is best done using the Google Chrome browser.
Contact
Contact Us by Phone:
General Legislative Questions:406.444.3064
Technical Questions (i.e. website, streaming):406-444-0912
Contact Us by Mail:
Montana State LegislatureState CapitolPO Box 201706Helena, MT 59620-1706
Search
Filter Results:
Google Analytics
The Montana Legislature uses Google Analytics to analyze web traffic. Google uses cookies to collect anonymous web traffic data, which the Montana Legislature uses to improve our online services, information and user experience. Through our use of the Google Analytics application, neither Montana Legislature nor Google collect personally identifiable information.
The following information may be automatically collected and retained when you view or search through Montana Legislature websites, or download information:
The Internet domain and Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using to access the site;
The type of browser and operating system used to visit the site;
The date and time of when you access the site; and
Which portions of the website you visit.
The data collected serves as part of our statistical analysis about the use of Montana Legislature websites so we may better design online services and improve access to information. We do not attempt to gain personally identifiable information about individual users and associate it with IP addresses. The State does not use the information collected to ascertain your personally identifiable information.
For additional details, refer to:
How Google uses data when you use partner sites or apps
Google Analytics Terms of Service
Google Privacy Policy
How Google uses cookies
State of Montana Operations Manual: Internet Privacy & Security Policy
Montana Code Annotated 2-17-505: Information Technology -- Internet Privacy Policy
